reliancegeneral.co.in 2014-12-31

# Privacy Policy

## Protecting the privacy

All information submitted by the visitors to the website of Reliance General Insurance shall be safeguarded and protected. Reliance General Insurance is committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality, accuracy and security of the personal information that it collects, uses, retains and discloses in the course of conducting business. This privacy policy will protect the data provided by you and will be used for purposes of processing your application, the assessment and processing of claims and any other administration relevant to any policy issued by Reliance General Insurance. By using this website you agree to the terms of this privacy statement. 

## Security Measures

Only authorized personnel have access to your information. Our systems and procedures are designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction of your information. Our commitment to security extends to the contracts and agreements that we sign with external suppliers and service providers. We will only retain your information for as long as required for the purposes for which it was collected and/or any legal or regulatory requirements.

## Use of the information collected

The information collected by us includes your contact information such as your name, address, and email address and other details as given in the registration page of our website. If you purchase a policy from us we will collect financial information such as credit card number and expiration date through the payment gateway of the credit card company or the Internet banking service of your bank. We also collect information such as beneficiary name, address and your relationship to the beneficiary when you buy a policy from us. This is required to maintain a record of your beneficiary details for your insurance with us.

By using this website you authorize us to contact you via email or phone on your contact details provided above and offer you information and services for the product you have opted for. You authorize us to call you for the mentioned purpose for a period of upto 30 days irrespective of whether you are registered with the NDNC registry.

We may collect, use and disclose your personal information to:

  * identify you
  * understand your needs
  * confirm your application information and assess your eligibility for products and services
  * provide you and/or your broker with ongoing services, establish and maintain communication, and to respond to your inquiries
  * investigate and settle your claims, and determine your eligibility for benefits
  * provide information that may be of interest to you
  * meet regulatory requirements

## Link to other websites

This page may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. While Reliance General Insurance website is subject to this privacy statement, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other Web sites that are linked to or from this Web site. Any information you provide to these third parties will be subject to their respective privacy policies. We therefore recommend that you read the privacy statement for each third party site you visit.

## Contact Us

If you have any comments or concerns regarding this privacy policy please contact:

Reliance General Insurance Company Limited  
Address: 570 Rectifier House, 1st Floor,  
Naigaum Cross Road,  
Next to Royal Industrial Estate, Wadala,  
Mumbai 400 031.  
Phone No: +91 - 022 - 30479600
